[
    {
        "Question": "mere",
        "Answer": "only",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "avid",
        "Answer": "enthusiasitc",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gather some momentum",
        "Answer": "made progress",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "elusive",
        "Answer": "difficult to catch",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unprecedented",
        "Answer": "unlike anything in the past",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concern",
        "Answer": "interest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barrier",
        "Answer": "impediment",
        "Options": "obstacle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "exposed",
        "Answer": "unprotected",
        "Options": "visible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "diverted",
        "Answer": "shifted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "severed",
        "Answer": "cut off",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "epitomize",
        "Answer": "exemplify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deluxe",
        "Answer": "lavish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "culminate",
        "Answer": "reach completion",
        "Options": "peak/ climax"
    },
    {
        "Question": "breed",
        "Answer": "reproduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deteriorated",
        "Answer": "got worse",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prized",
        "Answer": "valued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "approximately",
        "Answer": "roughtly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detach",
        "Answer": "separate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contrive",
        "Answer": "create",
        "Options": "invent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "unanticipated",
        "Answer": "not expected",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "target",
        "Answer": "objective",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "overshadowed",
        "Answer": "distracted from",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deliberate",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "just",
        "Answer": "fair",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incredible",
        "Answer": "unbelievable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compulsorily",
        "Answer": "by requirement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rebound",
        "Answer": "recovery",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "channel",
        "Answer": "direct",
        "Options": "guide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "preserving",
        "Answer": "maintaining",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "astonishing",
        "Answer": "incredible",
        "Options": "amazing/ surprising"
    },
    {
        "Question": "instructive",
        "Answer": "informative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intrinsically",
        "Answer": "fundamentally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ceased",
        "Answer": "stopped",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "isolated",
        "Answer": "widely separated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attest",
        "Answer": "confirm",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assertion",
        "Answer": "claim",
        "Options": "declaration/ statement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "forward-looking",
        "Answer": "progressive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "escalated",
        "Answer": "intensified",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "noticed",
        "Answer": "observed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ally with",
        "Answer": "link to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "acquire",
        "Answer": "obtain",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "empirical",
        "Answer": "based on observation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "perfected",
        "Answer": "completed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ancestor",
        "Answer": "relative from an earlier generation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assorted",
        "Answer": "various",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detected",
        "Answer": "discovered/ identified",
        "Options": "noticed/ revealed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "frigid",
        "Answer": "cold",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barely",
        "Answer": "just",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "nonetheless",
        "Answer": "however",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "rudimentary",
        "Answer": "basic",
        "Options": "undeveloped"
    },
    {
        "Question": "phenomenon",
        "Answer": "occurrence",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "favored",
        "Answer": "preferred",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "aggravate",
        "Answer": "annoy",
        "Options": "increase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "arrangement",
        "Answer": "configuration",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "posterity",
        "Answer": "future generations",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "explicit",
        "Answer": "obvious",
        "Options": "clear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enhanced",
        "Answer": "improved",
        "Options": "increased"
    },
    {
        "Question": "jointly",
        "Answer": "together",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "delicate",
        "Answer": "dainty",
        "Options": "fragile"
    },
    {
        "Question": "allude",
        "Answer": "refer",
        "Options": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conjunction",
        "Answer": "combination",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "a wealth of",
        "Answer": "an abundance of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "associates",
        "Answer": "connects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obtained",
        "Answer": "gathered",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "abrupt",
        "Answer": "sudden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "henceforth",
        "Answer": "from this time on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accelerate",
        "Answer": "speed up",
        "Options": "get faster"
    },
    {
        "Question": "radical",
        "Answer": "extreme",
        "Options": "fundamental"
    },
    {
        "Question": "emergency",
        "Answer": "crisis",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "indicative of",
        "Answer": "suggesting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "scale",
        "Answer": "size",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "largely renounces",
        "Answer": "generally rejects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "encourage",
        "Answer": "stimulate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contribute to",
        "Answer": "add to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attributes",
        "Answer": "ascribes/ credited",
        "Options": "characteristics/ properties"
    },
    {
        "Question": "subsequent",
        "Answer": "later",
        "Options": "following in time"
    },
    {
        "Question": "designate",
        "Answer": "assign",
        "Options": "identify"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disassemble",
        "Answer": "break up",
        "Options": "break apart"
    },
    {
        "Question": "established",
        "Answer": "qualified",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compelling",
        "Answer": "persuasive/ convincing",
        "Options": "forcing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "triggered",
        "Answer": "caused",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "termed",
        "Answer": "called",
        "Options": "known as"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inadequate",
        "Answer": "deficient",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intricate",
        "Answer": "complex",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "collide with",
        "Answer": "run into",
        "Options": "hit each other"
    },
    {
        "Question": "heterogeneous",
        "Answer": "varied",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "lodge",
        "Answer": "embed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sacred",
        "Answer": "holy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inhospitable",
        "Answer": "not suitable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dilute",
        "Answer": "reduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sequence",
        "Answer": "series",
        "Options": "order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "domain",
        "Answer": "field of expertise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "suspended",
        "Answer": "hung",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "central",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "apparatus",
        "Answer": "equipment",
        "Options": "device"
    },
    {
        "Question": "substantiated",
        "Answer": "confirmed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inconclusive",
        "Answer": "not decisive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "traumatic",
        "Answer": "upsetting",
        "Options": "highly stressful"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inevitable",
        "Answer": "certain/ necessary",
        "Options": "unavoidable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ingenuity",
        "Answer": "cleverness",
        "Options": ""
    }
]